[thunder rumbling]
[indistinct murmuring]
We weren't able to find out
what happened to Uvo,
but we did learn the chain user's name
and what he looks like.
Nothing on his abilities yet.
[Chrollo] Alright.
We'll be waiting in the lobby
of the hotel.
Looks like they found out
the chain user's identity.
-[both gasp]
-That just leaves three more.
Let's go.
We should go too.
[Gon] What do we do?
There isn't any point
in capturing Pakunoda now.
[Killua] If I were Kurapika,
I would switch targets.
If I wanted to crush the Troupe,
I'd go after the leader.
Melody is listening in
on the conversation,
so they should know where we're going.
It’s just a question of when he’ll attack.
We all need to be on the same page.
We need to be precise.
A second’s delay would be fatal.
[theme music playing]
INITIATIVE x AND x LAW
Let's wait right here.
[Killua] There are no opportunities
to attack.
They'll be watching anyone
who walks in the door.
I just hope Kurapika and Melody
beat us here.
-[Leorio] Come on!
-[gasps]
-[Leorio] Don't you know what time it is?
-Hmm?
Idiot! It's the Beitacle Hotel!
How many damn times
do I have to repeat myself? Well?
[Gon] Leorio!
Hmm? What are you looking at, kid? Huh?
-Should I kill him?
-Ignore him.
Look the other way.
What? You think this is a show? Scram!
Look. With failures like you
working for me,
my future’s about to get real dark.
[gasps]
Listen. I’m gonna close my eyes,
just this once.
-[gasps]
-One more mistake and you're fired!
You better get over to the hotel
by seven o’clock sharp. Do you hear me?
[both] It's a message!
[Killua] Seven sharp.
[Gon] We'll use darkness for cover.
[sighing]
I’ll dislocate my joints and get free.
I just need point-seven seconds to attack.
I'll have plenty of time!
It'll take a few seconds for their eyes
to adjust to the darkness
if the lights suddenly go out.
[radio DJ]
Alright, it's time for our last song.
This request comes from Kicchomu.
["Just Awake" by Fear and Loathing
in Las Vegas playing on radio]
[both] Three more minutes!
Everybody made it here.
Hey. What's this?
You boys got caught again?
[chuckles] Okay, I get it.
You changed your minds
and decided to join us, right?
Look, we didn't know anything
about your bounty.
It was canceled, wasn't it?
We just found out about it.
You were stalking us
and you screwed up again, huh?
You kids never learn.
I guess this must be fate at work.
[Killua] Two more minutes.
Well, let's be friends, okay?
-Fat chance!
-Huh?
We were only following you guys
just to get the reward.
And to be perfectly honest,
I don't even wanna look at you.
[Gon] Nice. Now we won't seem suspicious
when we close our eyes.
Yeah, me neither.
[chuckles] What do you think, boss?
They've got guts, don't they?
Their nerve reminds me of Uvo.
They’re just little kids.
They don’t even know enough to be afraid.
Anyway, describe the chain user to us.
First things first. Why don’t you
check them once again, Paku?
[both grunt softly]
Okay then. What should I ask?
Ask them, “what are you hiding?”
[Killua] Damn, that's a great question.
It's straight to the point,
and he can learn
all kinds of information from it.
[radio DJ] Well folks,
there's only one minute left
in this week's broadcast.
[Killua] One minute! We've gotta stall.
It's no use.
Your ability...
It lets you draw memories
out of whoever you touch, doesn't it?
Well, we're not hiding anything.
And even if-- [grunting]
I’ll find out soon enough,
so just be quiet.
Even if we did know something,
we'd hide it from you. It's not that hard.
We'll think about some--
Yeah. That’s what I thought.
[Pakunoda] You boys seem confused.
I extract the purest memories
that are beneath your consciousness.
I’m not browsing through
the surface thoughts you create.
My questions are specifically designed
to stimulate your memory.
They’re brought to the surface
the same way a stone tossed
into a pond stirs up sediment.
They’re original memories,
clean and unprocessed.
And I simply scoop them up.
Deceiving me is impossible.
[radio DJ] Tune in next week.
This is JFN, and it's 7:00 p.m.
[Killua] Here we go!
[grunting softly]
[Pakunoda] It's time to ask my question.
[both grunting]
-[Pakunoda] What are you hiding?
-[clock beeping]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[Killua] I see them
but they can't see us!
[Pakunoda grunting]
[Machi] The kid on the right is loose?
I can’t see!
So this was their plan?
Oh, no you don’t!
-[Gon yelling]
-[Killua] Gon!
I’ll have to kill her to break the thread!
[gasps]
My hand! She trapped it with her muscles!
[Machi] You're mine.
Seems your bloodlust gave you away.
The darkness can’t help you now.
[Gon] Killua!
[gasps]
Might as well give up.
What a pity.
Well, it was a good shot,
I'll give you that.
It came from the entrance.
[Shizuku] That guy was working with them?
Forget him! All we need now
are these two kids, right?
-Our eyes will adjust shortly.
-You're right.
But wait, where did the boss go?
[thunder crashing]
[Nobunaga] The boss is gone.
Shizuku, hold this one.
[Shizuku] Sure.
Are you okay, Paku?
He broke my left hand and a molar.
[Machi] We underestimated them.
You’re not gonna believe this,
but these kids--
[Nobunaga] Wait!
Pakunoda, it's for you.
DISCUSS THEIR MEMORIES AND I'LL KILL HIM.
[gasps]
Hey, what the hell is going on here?
[Pakunoda] We missed him
because he was disguised as a clerk.
No. That can’t be right.
The Boss should have been able
to evade a chain attack
from that distance without any trouble.
Except the abrupt plunge into darkness
must have delayed his reaction time
by a split second.
This attack was planned
to the last detail!
Either way, I was only able
to learn a few key words,
like “blackout” and “seven o’clock sharp."
And another thing that bothers me...
If these kids knew the chain user
all along,
then why didn’t my previous questioning
trigger any memories?
He must have been hiding his powers
not just from his enemies,
but from his friends, as well!
From that, we can surmise
that he’s most likely intelligent,
quick on his feet, secretive,
and above all, cold-blooded.
That tells me he probably isn’t bluffing.
He was prepared to sacrifice
a few precious seconds
just to leave me this message.
Which means it's true. It has to be.
His ally has the ability
to read human emotion
just by listening to heartbeats.
That ally is the reason he had time
to leave this message behind.
If I talk, he'll almost certainly
sacrifice his friends and kill the boss!
But if I don’t talk, then these kids
will still be valuable as hostages.
-[Nobunaga] Paku...
-We have a chance to rescue the boss.
-[Nobunaga] Paku!
-[gasps]
Don't say a word from here on out.
Got it?
Machi. You just focus
on your Nen threads. I’ll take this one.
[both] Kurapika did it!
Since he left us a message,
he’ll probably try
to contact us again soon.
Until he does, these two are our hostages.
[Chrollo] I am the head of the spider
and you are the legs.
Natural law dictates that the legs
must follow wherever the head goes.
But this is just the chain of command.
It doesn’t apply to my life or death.
If I happen to die,
one of you can replace me.
And there may come a time when a leg
has more importance than the head.
Make the right call.
My orders are priority.
However, my life and my death are not.
So, what’s key is survival of the whole.
Not the individual. Never forget that.
[Pakunoda] So what should we do now?
If I tell everyone that I learned
the chain user’s powers and weaknesses,
we could then use that information
to defeat him quite easily.
But if I do,
that makes Chrollo’s death more likely.
I’m sure Uvo faced a similar choice
when he died for the Spiders’ sake.
To die...
What did that fortune from the boss say?
Two choices...
Would speaking be considered a betrayal?
Or would lying?
What’s key is survival of the whole.
[Pakunoda] Right. I'm overthinking it.
[Machi] Paku...
I wouldn’t worry about this too much.
Until we know more,
you should just keep quiet.
Just hurry up, Phinks!
Somebody has captured the boss!
We still need you.
Even if that means...
betraying the Spiders.
We'll be fine.
A number of the enemy were injured.
So they’ll stay put until backup arrives.
-What are you looking at?
-Nothing.
I just didn't expect the chain user
to be a woman.
[Kurapika] Who said I was?
I thought you knew better
than to trust appearances.
Regardless, you should watch what you say.
Since it may well be the last thing
out of your mouth.
You aren’t going to kill me.
Not after you left
your precious friends behind.
I may appear calm and composed
but I will not ignore your threats!
[Leorio] Kurapika! That's enough.
[Chrollo]
The girl's fortune failed to mention this.
Therefore, this event
isn't significant enough to matter,
or else I am quite certain
that it would have come up.
-[Kurapika] Bastard!
-Kurapika!
[Leorio] If you kill him,
I'll kick your ass, you hear me?
Should I explain further?
This situation is nothing.
It's no different
than an afternoon coffee break.
In fact, it’s quite peaceful.
Kurapika, calm down!
Nothing has changed!
We’re on equal footing now.
Equal? I’m afraid you’re quite
mistaken in that regard.
Your assumption is completely wrong.
I have no value as a hostage.
Shut up. If you insist on babbling--
[Melody] It's the truth!
Everything that he’s told us
so far is sincere.
[Chrollo] There you have it.
This is reality.
You’re the one who’s cornered.
What do you mean by that?
I mean his heartbeat is perfectly normal.
He’s not shaken by any of this.
He’s not worried or scared, even of death.
He’s accepted his destiny.
I can hear that he walks with death
every single day of his life.
How can he produce such a sound?
Make it stop!
I can't take any more!
I don't want to listen
to either one of you!
Oh, Melody...
He truly believes that he has
no real value as a hostage whatsoever.
And yet the fact remains
that he’s the leader.
[Kurapika] What are you?
What are you people?
The Spiders.
Okay, so what happened?
The lights went out.
The boss was captured in the confusion.
[Kortopi]
Here's the message from the chain user.
[Feitan] Why didn't you go after him?
-Machi and Paku were injured.
-[Feitan] So?
So, he has allies who happen
to be pro Hunters.
So?
Come on! Read between the lines,
damn it!
It proves that we can use
these kids as hostages.
If we give chase and we let them escape,
it's all over!
The chains Uvo couldn’t break out of
are probably the ones
that captured the Boss.
He can’t escape on his own.
[Phinks] Probably?
I told you it was dark!
By the time our eyes adjusted,
the boss had vanished.
And with these kids here,
we weren’t in a position to move!
Fine, fine. But let’s not point fingers.
For now, we just need a plan.
[Kurapika] Were you the leader
of the Troupe five years ago?
When they mercilessly slaughtered
the Kurta of the Scarlet Eyes?
Ugh! Answer me!
Are those the chains you killed Uvo with?
What were his last words?
I don't remember them.
That isn't true, is it?
Am I right, Miss?
But I can relate. I feel the same.
I have nothing to say to you.
-[Leorio] He's trying to provoke you!
-[Kurapika] Damn it!
-[Leorio] Don't fall for it!
Damn it!
[Chrollo] That proves it.
I'm surprised.
The chain user has a weakness.
One that I can exploit.
[phone ringing]
It's from the boss' phone.
[all gasping]
[Phinks] Hello?
I have three demands.
[Phinks] You the chain user?
The general rule is that you will do
as I tell you to.
If you don't obey,
I'll kill your leader immediately.
First, do not come after us.
Second, do not harm the two hostages.
Third, put Pakunoda on the phone.
Can I ask you something first?
It's about your second demand.
See, the hostages started putting up
a bit of a fight
so we had to break a few bones.
[snickering]
-[Kurapika] Then we're done here.
-[hangs up]
[hits redial]
[Kurapika] What?
Sorry, I was lying.
Both of them are okay.
This is your last chance.
Try to take it seriously.
Now put Pakunoda on the phone.
[Phinks grunting] Ow!
Yes, hello?
You're the only one allowed to hear
what I have to say.
Move away from the others.
Did you make contact with Squala?
[Pakunoda] Yes.
[Kurapika]
So, you're aware of Melody, then?
[Pakunoda] I am.
[Kurapika] Good, this won’t take long.
Listen carefully.
I forbid all further communication
with the others.
No talking, gestures, writing,
signals or eye contact.
None of that is allowed.
Come to the place I designate
and come alone.
If your heart rate changes
in the slightest, I will kill the hostage.
Understood?
Hand off the phone.
Anyone but the man from before.
[Nobunaga] Uh, hello?
[Kurapika] I'm going to meet
with Pakunoda alone.
The rest of you return to your hideout.
All ten Troupe members must be there.
If one is missing, I'll kill the hostage.
-Understand?
-Yeah.
-[Kurapika] Put Pakunoda back on.
-Take it.
[Kurapika] Come to Lingon Airport.
You have until eight.
Remember, you’re to come completely alone.
[Chrollo] Don't hesitate, Pakunoda.
Bring everyone.
He’s sure to put his friends
before his mission.
Hey, Paku!
[Nobunaga] Wait!
Let Paku go there by herself.
We’re gonna go back to the hideout.
Those were his orders.
Who cares about that?
He just said if we disobeyed,
he was gonna kill the boss!
Are you an idiot? If that happens,
we'll kill the chain user.
And that will be that.
It's what the boss would want us to do.
Your way of thinking is an insult
to the Spiders, Nobunaga.
Let’s quit wasting time
and follow Pakunoda.
It’s the only choice we have!
He does have a point. There’s no reason
that we should let Paku go alone.
If we keep following his orders,
the fortunes will come true.
Look, I’m with Nobunaga on this one.
We should all follow his orders for now.
-[Kortopi] She's right.
-For now?
How long's that gonna be?
Until half our limbs are gone or what?
[scoffs] Hey, Shizuku, what do you think?
[Shizuku] Disagreements are settled
with a coin toss.
[Phinks]
A coin toss isn’t gonna cut it right now!
Hmm, I think I’ll have to side
with Nobunaga.
'Cause I don’t want the boss
to die right now.
Same goes for Pakunoda.
I'm sure she feels the same way.
I suppose that's why she left
without saying a word.
I don't believe this.
It’s like talking to a wall.
If it was up to me, I’d kill you right now
but Pakunoda comes first.
[Nobunaga] Wait!
I’m warning you, take one more step
and I’ll cut you down.
Oh, yeah? I'd like to see you try it.
Troupe members are not allowed to fight.
[Phinks] Aren't you on Nobunaga's side?
That's what my heart tells me.
But the rules are the rules.
You break the rules,
you reject the spider.
We’d be rejecting the Boss, too.
I don't wanna do either of those things.
-[phone ringing]
-It's the chain-user.
Here. Let me take it.
Yeah, this is--
[Kurapika] Put a hostage on the phone.
[Phinks] You little...
Here.
[Kurapika] Are all of them together?
[Killua] Right now, they are.
But they've been talking
about going after Pakunoda...
You'd better watch your mouth, kid.
Still there?
Be at your hideout in half an hour.
I’m sure you’ll be tempted
to try something,
but then your boss will die.
I'll call again soon.
[Shizuku] Guess we can't follow Paku now.
[Phinks] Damn it!
[Franklin] The boss will die
if all ten of us aren’t together?
And he’s using the hostages
as messengers. That’s pretty smart.
[Hisoka] This is the perfect opportunity
to fight the boss.
But if I leave, he'll die.
Well, there you have it.
I'll need some help.
[Illumi] Sure, alright. I’ve known you
a little longer than Chrollo.
[narrator]
Kurapika’s revenge has come to fruition.
And his confrontation with the Troupe
has reached its final stage.
[theme music playing]
-[Gon] Coming up, Gon...
-[Killua] And Killua's...
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I'm Gon!
-I'm Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, you're gonna meet Pakunoda!
She's a Specialist
and she has the power to see memories
whenever she touches people or things.
She also has the ability to conjure
memories into bullets and shoot them.
[both] Memory Bomb!
[Gon] Next time:
"Signal to Retreat."
[Killua cackling]
-[Gon] What are you doing, Killua?
-[cackling continues]
[Gon] Maybe we should retreat.